https://www.wh.group/na/meta/privacy_policy/

PaperPaperPaper Bag ProductionPaper Sack ProductionWovenWovenFabric ProductionWoven Bag ProductionFilmFilmFilm ProductionFilm PrintingFilm Bag ProductionForm-Fill-Seal-Sacks (FFS)Our ProductsExtrusionExtrusionBlown film linesCast film linesWinderStretching unitWoven LinesRetrofitsPrintingPrintingFlexo printing pressesGravure printing pressesFlexo tail-end printerAssistence SystemsConvertingConvertingTuberBottomerMaterial Flow& PalletisingConverting systemsForm, Fill and SealSmall bags/ Carrier Bag MachinesSmart Deals
ServiceSupport & MaintenanceSupport & Maintenance24 / 7 Remote ServiceVisual AssistanceService VisitsDie Cleaning ServicePartsPartsOriginal PartsParts IdentificationRetrofits & UpgradesRetrofits & UpgradesExtrusion RetrofitsRetrofits for non W&H LinesTraining & EventsTraining & EventsIndividual TrainingStandard TrainingTechnology EventsService ContractsService ContractsDigital ServicesDigital ServicesRUBY IoT SystemIoT System RUBYIoT System RUBYThis is RUBYRUBY GoRUBY CheckRUBY TrackRUBY GaincompanyW&H in North AmericaW&H in North AmericaW&H CorporationContactsW&H GroupW&H GroupHistorySustainabilityProduction & QualityTechnology CenterPackaging 4.0News & EventsNews & EventsEventsE-MagazineMediaWall of FameE-NewsletterConversionsW&H Virtual ExpoW&H Virtual ExpoW&H at K2019
ContactsYour Contacts in North AmericaYour Contacts in North AmericaYour Contacts worldwideYour Contacts worldwideAcademyAbout W&H AcademyAbout W&H AcademyCertified TrainerCustomer TrainingsCustomer TrainingsInternal QualificationInternal QualificationVocational TrainingVocational Training
W&H North America | English
metaprivacy_policy
Privacy Policy
The protection of your privacy is of greatest importance to Windmöller & Hölscher KG.In the following, we would like to provide you with an overview of the processing of your personal data as well as your associated rights in accordance with Articles 13, 14 European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).The information is presented on general and purpose-specific information, depending on which target group (e.g. website visitors, business partners, applicants) you belong to.
Responsible authorityThe responsible authority according to European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), German Federal Data Protection Act (BDSG) as well as the Telecommunications Act (TMG) is:Windmöller & Hölscher KGMünsterstraße 5049525 LengerichTelefon: +49 5481 14-0Fax: +49 5481 14-2649Email: info@wuh-group.comData Protection OfficerIf you have any questions or comments about this privacy statement, on the subject of data protection in general or on asserting your rights, please do not hesitate to contact our company data protection officer via email datenschutz@wuh-group.com or by post at the address shown above.Scope of the collection and the use of your data including the purposes of the processing operation Depending on the target group you belong to (e.g. website visitor, business partner, applicant), below you find each of one section with information concerning privacy policy.
Website visitors
Visit our websiteBasicly it is possible to visit our website without providing personal data.To implement and guarantee the functionality of the website, we process the data transmitted to us by your Internet browser. These include the date and time of your visit to the website, the IP address, country of origin of the IP address, content of the request (specific page), browser settings, the amount of data transmitted in each case, the website from which the request comes, browser, language and version of the browser software and the operating system used.Newsletter On our website we offer you to receive information about our offers by newsletter.For the registration process we use the so-called double opt-in procedure. After you have given us your email address, we will send you a confirmation message to this email address. Only when you click on the confirmation link contained therein will your email address be taken into account when sending the newsletter. This ensures that only the actual owner of the email address can order the newsletter. The data processing within the scope of the newsletter is based on your consent. You have the right to revoke this consent at any time with effect for the future.Here you can unsubscribe from the newsletter and thus revoke your consent.We use MailChimp as our platform for marketing automation. By giving your consent for the dispatch of our newsletter, you confirm that the information provided by you will be passed on to MailChimp for processing in accordance with MailChimp's data protection declaration.You can find MailChimp's privacy policy at: mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/. MailChimp has submitted to the EU-US Privacy Shield www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-Framework.Use of our contact dataYou can contact us directly via the e-mail addresses / telephone numbers provided on our Internet pages. We collect, process and use the personal data and information provided by you by e-mail / telephone exclusively for the processing of your request. This correspondence will be stored in compliance with the statutory retention periods and deleted after any retention periods have expired.Use of cookiesWe use cookies on our website. Cookies are small text files that are sent from our web server to your browser during your visit to our website and stored on your computer for later retrieval. The purpose of these cookies is to continue to identify your computer during a visit to our website when switching from one of our websites to another and to be able to determine the end of your visit (so-called transient cookies).Of course, you can also view our website without cookies. Internet browsers are regularly set to accept cookies. You can deactivate the use of cookies at any time via the settings of your browser. Please use the help functions of your Internet browser to find out how you can change these settings. Please note that individual functions of our website may not function if you have deactivated the use of cookies. We do not collect or store personal data in cookies in this context. We also do not use any techniques that associate information generated by cookies with user data.Use of google analyticsIf you have given your consent, Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google LLC ("Google") is used on this website. The use includes the "Universal Analytics" operating mode. This makes it possible to assign data, sessions and interactions across multiple devices to a pseudonymous user ID and thus analyze a user's activities across devices.Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users interact with the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is usually transferred to a Google server in the USA and stored there. However, if IP anonymisation is activated on this website, Google will reduce your IP address within Member States of the European Union or in other states party to the Agreement on the European Economic Area beforehand. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be transmitted to a Google server in the USA and shortened there. We would like to point out that on this website Google Analytics has been extended to include IP anonymisation in order to ensure anonymous collection of IP addresses (so-called IP masking). The IP address transmitted by your browser in the context of Google Analytics is not merged with other Google data. For more information on terms of use and data protection, please visit https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html or https://policies.google.com/?hl=e.You can also prevent Google from collecting the data generated by the cookie and relating to your use of the website (including your IP address) and from processing this data by Google by downloading and installing the Browser Add-on. Opt-out cookies will prevent future collection of your data when you visit this website. To prevent Universal Analytics from collecting data across different devices, you must opt-out on all systems used. If you click here, the opt-out cookie will be set: Disable Google AnalyticsFurther information on the terms of use and data protection can be found at http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/de.html and https://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/respectively. We would like to point out that on this website Google Analytics has been extended by the code "anonymizeIp" in order to guarantee a pseudonymised recording of IP addresses (so-called IP masking).Social-Media-Plug-insWe currently use the following social media plug-ins: LinkedIn, Xing and YouTube.We use the so-called two-click solution. This means that when you visit our site, no personal data is initially passed on to the plugin providers. You have the possibility to communicate directly with the provider of the plug-in by clicking on the logo of the respective plug-in provider in the footer of our homepage. Only if you click on the logo and thereby activate it will the plug-in provider receive the information that you have called up the corresponding website of our online service. In addition, the data mentioned under topic Visit to our website of this declaration will be transmitted.In the case of Xing, the IP address is anonymized immediately after collection, according to the respective provider in Germany. By activating the plug-in, personal data is transferred from you to the respective plug-in provider and stored there (for US providers in the USA). Since the plug-in provider collects data mainly via cookies, we recommend that you delete all cookies before clicking on the grayed-out box using your browser's security settings.We have no influence on the data collected and data processing processes, nor are we aware of the full extent of data collection, the purposes of processing, the storage periods. We also have no information on the deletion of the data collected by the plug-in provider.The plug-in providers save the data collected about you as user profiles and use these for the purposes of advertising, market research and/or demand-oriented design of its website. Such an evaluation takes place in particular (also for not logged in users) for the representation of demand-fair advertisement and in order to inform other users of the social network about your activities on our website.You have a right of objection to the creation of these user profiles, whereby you must contact the respective plug-in provider to exercise this right. Through the plug-ins we offer you the possibility to interact with social networks and other users, so that we can improve our offer and make it more interesting for you as a user(Legal basis as mentioned below).The data is transferred regardless of whether you have an account with the plug-in provider and are logged in there. If you are logged in with the plug-in provider, your data collected with us will be directly assigned to your existing account with the plug-in provider. If you click the activated button and, for example, link the page, the plug-in provider also stores this information in your user account and shares it publicly with your contacts. We recommend that you log out regularly after using a social network, especially before activating the button, as this way you can avoid being assigned to your profile with the plug-in provider.For more information on the purpose and scope of data collection and its processing by the plug-in provider, please refer to the data protection declarations of these providers as notified below. They will also provide you with further information about your rights in this regard and setting options to protect your privacy.Addresses of the respective plug-in providers and URL with their data protection information:LinkedIn Corporation, 2029 Stierlin Court, Mountain View, California 94043, USA; www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policyLinkedIn has submitted to the EU-US Privacy Shield, www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-FrameworkXing AG, Gänsemarkt 43, 20354 Hamburg, Germany; privacy.xing.com/de/datenschutzerklaerungYouTube LLC, 901 Cherry Ave., San Bruno, California 94066, USA; policies.google.com/privacyYouTube has submitted to the EU-US Privacy Shield, https://www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-FrameworkIntegration of Google MapsOn this website we use the offer of Google Maps. This allows us to display interactive maps directly on the website and enables you to conveniently use the map function.By visiting the website, Google receives the information that you have called up the corresponding subpage of our website. In addition, the data mentioned under point Visit of our website of this declaration above will be transmitted. This is regardless of whether Google provides a user account that you are logged in with or whether no user account exists. If you are logged in to Google, your information will be directly associated with your account. If you do not wish to be associated with your profile on Google, you must log out before activating the button. Google stores your data as usage profiles and uses them for purposes of advertising, market research and/or demand-oriented design of its website. Such evaluation takes place in particular (even for unlogged-in users) to provide demand-oriented advertising and to inform other users of the social network about your activities on our website. You have the right to object to the creation of these user profiles, whereby you must contact Google to exercise this right.For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and its processing by the plug-in provider, please refer to the provider's privacy policy. There you will also find further information about your rights in this regard and setting options to protect your privacy: www.policies.google.com/privacyGoogle also processes your personal data in the USA and has submitted to the EU-US Privacy Shield, www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-FrameworkLegal basisWe process your personal data in accordance withArticle 6 paragraph 1 letter f) of the GDPR, insofar as we have a justified interest in this, insofar as your interests or fundamental rights, which require the protection of your personal data, do not predominate. The use of the above mentioned cookies, the use of tools to evaluate your usage behavior on our website and the integration of social media plug-ins are examples of how we guarantee and optimize the functionality of our website.Article 6 paragraph 1 letter a) of the GDPR, in so far as you have granted your consent. This includes sending of a newsletter. We process your personal data only for the purposes for which we have received or collected this data. If we intend to process data for other purposes that are not founded on consent or a legal provision, we shall provide you with information about this other purpose prior to further processing in accordance with Articles 13, 14 of the GDPR.Forwarding within Windmöller & HölscherGroup and forwarding to third parties/third countriesYour personal data will only be passed on if it is necessary for the above mentioned purposes, for example to the marketing department for advertising purposes, to supporting service providers and to law enforcement authorities if there is a reporting, proof or legal obligation to do so. Service providers within the scope of order processing, such as service providers for IT services, are contractually obliged to comply with the applicable data protection requirements pursuant to Article 28 GDPR.Duration of data storageWe process the data for as long as this is required for the respective purpose. To the extent that your data is subject to tax, commercial law or other legal retention obligations, the data shall be stored until the expiry of the aforementioned deadlines. If we have saved your data for advertising purposes, we shall delete this data at the time at which you revoke your consent to further advertising contact. This does not apply as long as this data is subject to a statutory retention obligation.
Business partner
We process personal data which we receive from you within the scope of a business relationship or when establishing a business relationship. In addition, we process data that we have obtained from public directories (e.g. press, commercial registry, Internet) in compliance with the data protection legal guidelines.Legal basisWe process your personal data in accordance withArticle 6 paragraph 1 letter b) of the GDPR for the purpose of contract fulfillment. This includes sending information and offers in the pre-contractual stage provided that you have made inquiries with us regarding our products/services as well as in the post-contractual stage when processing complaints, spare parts deliveries and services. Article 6 paragraph 1 letter c) of the GDPR, for the fulfilment of legal obligations. These include, for example, obligations under trade and tax laws, EU regulations, comparisons (compliance checks) with national and international anti-terror lists.Article 6 paragraph 1 letter f) of the GDPR, to the extent that we have a legitimate interest therein, unless your interests or fundamental rights that require the protection of your personal data outweigh this. This includes, for example, the transmission of data within the corporate group for internal administrative purposes, guaranteeing IT security and IT operations, requests regarding satisfaction, assessment of the creditworthiness of the business partner. Article 6 paragraph 1 letter a) of the GDPR, in so far as you have granted your consent. We process your personal data only for the purposes for which we have received or collected this data. If we intend to process data for other purposes that are not founded on consent or a legal provision, we shall provide you with information about this other purpose prior to further processing in accordance with Articles 13, 14 of the GDPR.Forwarding within of Windmöller & HölscherGroup and forwarding to third parties/third countriesYour personal data will only be transferred within Windmöller & Hölscher KG if it is necessary for the above-mentioned purposes to corresponding departments within Windmöller & Hölscher KG which require it, to subsidiaries of Windmöller & Hölscher KG which will look after you as a business partner in your area and outside Windmöller & Hölscher KG to supporting service providers such as logistics companies, financial service providers, insurance companies, legal advisors as well as to financial authorities, law enforcement agencies, in case as there is a reporting, verification or legal obligation to do so.Service providers within the scope of order processing, such as service providers for IT services, are contractually obliged to comply with the applicable data protection requirements pursuant to Article 28 GDPR.Duration of data storageWe process the data for as long as this is required for the respective purpose. As long as your data is subject to tax, commercial law or other legal storage obligations, the data shall be stored until the expiry of the above mentioned deadlines. If we have saved your data for advertising purposes, we shall delete this data at the time at which you revoke your consent to further advertising contact. This does not apply as long as this data is subject to a legal storage obligation.
Applicants
We process personal data which we receive from you within the scope of application procedure. This includes in particular any data and information out of your curriculum vitae (full name, nationality), application letter (contact data e.g. address, telephone number, and e-mail address), certificates (e.g. qualification, grades), certificates of participation and assessments from third-parties (e.g. employer references). In addition, we process data concerning a severe disability or previous conviction which you indicated in your application.Legal basisWe process your personal data in accordance withArticle 6 paragraph 1 letter b) of the GDPR in connection with § 26 BDSG (new) for the purpose of contract fulfillment this means for creation or implementation of the working relationship.Article 6 paragraph 1 letter f) of the GDPR, to the extent that we have a legitimate interest therein, unless your interests or fundamental rights that require the protection of your personal data outweigh this. This includes, for example, the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims. Article 6 paragraph 1 letter a) of the GDPR in connection with § 26 para. 2 BDSG (new), in so far as you have granted your consent. This includes, for example, the storage of your data beyond the legally required period.Article 6 paragraph 1 letter c) of the GDPR in connection with § 26 BDSG, to satisfy our legal obligations as employer especially in the areas of tax and social insurance law in case of employment contract.We process your personal data only for the purposes for which we have received or collected this data. If we intend to process data for other purposes that are not founded on consent or a legal provision, we shall provide you with information about this other purpose prior to further processing in accordance with Articles 13, 14 of the GDPR.Forwarding within of Windmöller & Hölscher Group and forwarding to third parties/third countriesAs part of the application process, your data may be forwarded by e-mail to responsible employees within the Windmöller & Hölscher Group who are involved in the application process. In principle, data will not be transferred to third countries unless your application relates to jobs advertised by our group of companies in third countries or you have given us your consent.Duration of data storageWe store personal data for the duration of the application process. If no employment relationship is established, we delete the data after completion of the application process (e.g. notification of the rejection decision) within the statutory time limits, unless longer storage due to litigation is required. In case that you have agreed to your personal data being stored for a longer period of time, we will store it in accordance with your declaration of consent. If an employment relationship is established following the application procedure, your data will, as far as necessary and permissible, initially continue to be stored and then transferred to the personal file.Non-availability of dataProviding of your personal data is necessary for initiation and if applicable conclusion of an employment contract. Without this data, we are not able to process your application and to conclude a contract with you.
Visitors of events (references to Photos)
At events of the Windmöller & Hölscher Group (as organizer or cooperation partner) we collect personal data from you (surname, first name, e-mail address etc.) which is required for participation and for even execution. We reserve the right to create, process and distribute photo, video and audio recordings of speakers, participants and guests for public relations purposes, provided these do not contradict in individual cases. This will be indicated in a suitable manner both at the electronic event registration and at the event location. We will inform you about the photo processing and photo publication of your personal data and the data protection claims and rights to which you are entitled.We process your personal data in accordance withArticle 6 paragraph 1 letter f) of the GDPR, to the extent that we have a legitimate interest The collection, storage and forwarding of data is carried out with justified interest. In individual cases, this will be weighed against other interests involved if it is opposed by an interest worthyof protection. Publication takes place on the basis of §§ 22, 23 KUG.Our legitimate interest includes the documentation of corporate events and trade fairs, in particular for press and public relations work and to present the company's activities in order to increase awareness, strengthen the brand and promote participation in comparable events and activities. The implementation takes place through the production of photos, image and sound recordings of events. This will be indicated in a suitable manner both at the electronic event registration and at the event location.We process your personal data only for the purposes for which we have received or collected this data. If we intend to process data for other purposes that are not founded on consent or a legal provision, we shall provide you with information about this other purpose prior to further processing in accordance with Articles 13, 14 of the GDPR.Forwarding within/outside of Windmöller & Hölscher KG and forwarding to a third countryWe publish the photos/videos on the following channels: websites, advertising material, advertisements in print magazines, online banner advertising, direct mailings, e-mail newsletters, third-party press reports, social media (Twitter, LinkedIn, Xing, Youtube).Duration of data storageWe process the data for as long as this is required for the respective purpose.
Visitors and users of our webshop
In our webshop you will find information about spare parts and have the possibility to order them online.In order to be able to place orders, it is necessary to set up a password-protected customer account. This contains an overview of transacted orders and active order processes. If you leave the online shop as a customer, you will be logged out automatically.We as operator assume no liability for password abuse, unless this was caused by us as operator ourselves.All data which you enter in our registration/contact form within the framework of order processing will be stored. This includes, for example, company/customer number, first name/last name, e-mail address.Use of EcondaOn W&H Webshop e use the web analysis service econda GmbH (Zimmerstr. 6, 76137 Karlsruhe, Germany, Managing Director: Christian Hagemeyer, Commercial Register: Amtsgericht Mannheim HRB 110559) to analyze and regularly improve the usage. The statistics obtained allow us to improve our services and make them more interesting for you as a user.Cookies (see also "Use of cookies" above for details) are stored on your computer for this evaluation. The information collected in this way is stored exclusively on the responsible person's server in Germany. You can adjust the evaluation by deleting existing cookies and preventing the storage of cookies. If you prevent the storage of cookies, we would like to point out that you may not be able to use this website to its full extent.You will be used for your Cookie preferences after logging into the Webshop. If you wish to opt out, please click “prevent capture"to place the Econda deactivation cookie in your browser:
Attention: If you delete your cookies, the Opt-Out-Cookie will also be deleted and may have to be reactivated by you.The Econda program is an open source project. You can obtain information on data protection from the third party provider at: https://www.econda.de/service/datenschutz/Legal basisWe process your personal data in accordance with Article 6 paragraph 1 letter b) of the GDPR for the purpose of contract fulfillment. This includes sending information and offers in the pre-contractual stage provided that you have made inquiries with us regarding our products/services as well as in the post-contractual stage when processing complaints, spare parts orders, deliveries and services. Article 6 paragraph 1 letter f) of the GDPR, to the extent that we have a legitimate interest therein, unless your interests or fundamental rights that require the protection of your personal data outweigh this. This includes, for example, the transmission of data within the corporate group for internal administrative purposes, requests regarding satisfaction, assessment of the credit quality of the business party.Article 6 paragraph 1 letter a) of the GDPR, in so far as you have granted your consent.Forwarding within of Windmöller & Hölscher Group and forwarding to third parties/third countriesYour personal data will only be transferred within Windmöller & Hölscher KG if it is necessary for the above-mentioned purposes to specialist departments within Windmöller & Hölscher KG which need it, to subsidiaries of Windmöller & Hölscher KG which will look after you as a business partner in your area and outside Windmöller & Hölscher KG to supporting service providers such as logistics companies, financial service providers, insurance companies, legal advisors as well as to financial authorities, law enforcement agencies insofar as there is a reporting, verification or legal obligation to do so. Service providers within the scope of order processing, such as service providers for IT services, are contractually obliged to comply with the applicable data protection requirements pursuant to Article 28 GDPR.Duration of data storageWe process the data for as long as this is required for the respective purpose, e.g. provision of our online services and the associated services. To the extent that your data is subject to tax, commercial law or other legal retention obligations, the data shall be stored until the expiry of the aforementioned deadlines. If we have saved your data for advertising purposes, we shall delete this data at the time at which you revoke your consent to further advertising contact. This does not apply as long as this data is subject to a statutory retention obligation.
Data SecurityWindmöller & Hölscher KG takes all technical and organizational precaotions in order to ensure that your personal data is protected against unintentional or unlawful deletion, alteration, or loss and against unauthorized disclosure or access.In order to protect your data, some offers on our website are processed via a secure server using state-of-the-art encryption methods (SSL/TLS) using HTTPS. You can tell that your browser uses this secure transmission by the fact that the Internet address starts with "https" and a small lock symbol that is (normally) displayed in the address line of your browser window. If the lock is closed, it is a secure transmission. In this case, some browsers show the address bar or part of it in green.Assertion of your rightsYou have the right to free information about your stored data and, under certain conditions, a right to limitation of data processing, correction, deletion or transfer of this data. Should you submit an information request, we ask for your understanding if we request proof of your identity. If you have granted us your consent to data processing, this can be revoked at any time with effect for the future. Furthermore, you also have the right to file a complaint with a supervisory authority if you are of the opinion that the processing of the corresponding personal data takes place in violation of the GDPR.The supervisory authority responsible for Windmöller & Hölscher KG is:State Commissioner for Data Protection and Freedom of Information North Rhine-WestphaliaKavalleriestr. 2-4Germany, 40213 DüsseldorfRight of objectionIn accordance with article 21 paragraphs 1 and 2 of the GDPR, you have the right to object to the processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes without indication of reasons. If we process your data in order to safeguard legitimate interests, you may object to this processing for reasons related to your particular situation. We shall no longer process your personal data unless we can prove compelling legitimate grounds for our processing which outweigh your interests, rights and freedoms or the processing serves the exercise or defense of legal claims.Links to other websitesOur website also contains links to other websites. If you are redirected to another website by clicking on one of the links, the data protection declaration of Windmöller & Hölscher KG no longer applies, but that of the respective website operator.Changes to the data protection declarationChanges to the data protection declaration We reserve the right to change this privacy policy to adapt it to new functions on the website or a changed legal situation. Your visit to our website is subject to the current version at the time.09/2019
